tryootech.com 2018-04-14

# Privacy Policy - Tryootech

#### **What information or data we collect?**

we collect information entered by you on our website, it may be your email address, name or your website URL address.

You enter information for Subscribing our newsletter, fill out a form to contact us or comment on our posts, you may visit our website without providing any information to us.

Third party vendor Google may use the cookie to serve ads on your website. You can opt out from this by visiting Google ad and content network.

We do not sell, trade or transfer your emails or information to third party websites or vendors. we use all security and safety measures for your best and better user experience.

**Why we take information from you?**

Information provided by you is used to enrich your experience with our blog or website. We provide regular content which provides value to you. Our first preference is user experience and satisfaction.

Third party Links on our blog.

We do use third party links on our website, which helps our users, subscribers or readers to navigate directly from the page. They need not go and search for the content while they are reading.

All third party websites have their own privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. We are responsible for our privacy policy.

This privacy policy is responsible for online data collected from our website not offline.

**Do we use cookies?**

yes, we use cookies. Cookies are the small files used by the service provider to transfer it to your hard drive via your web browser if you allow it. Use of cookie will help browser to remember/capture some information and recognize your browser.

Terms & Condition:

We also update our privacy policy. if we will update then you can see our privacy policy here only on this page.

Last updated: 1/9/2017

If you want to know about the author and [www.tryootech.com](http://www.tryootech.com/) you can visit [About Us](http://tryootech.com/about-us/) page.

Also, check our **Disclaimer  **page for limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.tryootech.com](http://www.tryootech.com/)

If there is any question related to Privacy Policy you can contact us @ admin@tryootech.com
